DAVID B. STOCKER

TECHNOLOGIST

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with experience in layout and typography (web and print), sales and marketing, project management, and collaborative office experience (I'm a team player). First languages: Python, LilyPond, HTML, SQL; Second Languages: JavaScript, CSS

MORE ABOUT ME

CONTACT

(804) 335-4241

coffeemetalcode@gmail.com

github: https://github.com/dbstocker
portfolio: https://dbstocker.github.io/
linkedin: https://bit.ly/2zmSUiB

twitter: @dbstocker

North Chesterfield, Virginia

PROJECTS

Foodchain - https://bit.ly/2BaR98i
Moodster - https://bit.ly/2Sgc2s5
Metal Attack RPG - https://bit.ly/2CUngJe

EDUCATION

Coding Boot Camp - UR

B.Mus in Guitar Performance, Minor in Religious Studies - VCU

MOOCs in Software development, including SQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Python, and others

SKILLS

Full Stack, MERN Stack, Interactive Websites, Web Apps, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, MySQL, MongoDB, Bootstrap and other CSS Frameworks, Flexbox, Mobile / Responsive Web Design

EXPERIENCE

2018 - NOW FULL STACK DEVELOPER coffee | metal | code

(Freelance)

2015 - NOW ACCOUNT COORDINATOR -PROFORMA STAND OUT BRANDING

- Maintain visual databases of inventory, past orders, and client layout information
- Coordinate with e-commerce and web development teams to manage jacksgear.com and qdobagear.com online stores
- Technical resource for collaborators and team members, including the franchise owner
- Manage multiple, simultaneous projects in Experiential Marketing / Branding
- Identify and remedy inefficiencies in office practices and workflow

2001 - 2015 SELF EMPLOYED | MUSIC PRINT PUBLISHING

- Music Transcription and Typesetting for Hal Leonard Corp and others
- Multiple Enterprise Software Packages, including text-based and markup-based packages
- Expense Tracking, Invoicing, and Collections